<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politics on My Dad&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://mydadsblog.com/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politics on My Dad&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mydadsblog.com/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I Have a Friend</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/i-have-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/i-have-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>I have a friend (besides you) that produces TV shows. He told me something that depressed him, and myself. The TV network that his shows are produced under had to change the script of the shows to accommodate their audience. Their audience is skewed to one side of our political divide. He needed to change the flow of the script to not emphasize that COVID-19 was a real fact because that is what their audience believes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insurrection</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/insurrection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/insurrection/</guid>
      <description>14th amendment in part:
 No person shall be a Senator or Representative in Congress, or elector of President and Vice President, or hold any office, civil or military, under the United States, or under any State, who, having previously taken an oath, as a member of Congress, or as an officer of the United States, or as a member of any State legislature, or as an executive or judicial officer of any State, to support the Constitution of the United States, shall have engaged in insurrection or rebellion against the same, or given aid or comfort to the enemies thereof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Even if / Boy Was I Wrong</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/so-even-if-boy-was-i-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/so-even-if-boy-was-i-wrong/</guid>
      <description>(This was two emails, before and after the insurrection.)
So Even if (Jan 5) If any state’s electoral vote were excluded, the law also says it is excluded from the total. Thus Trump would need to exclude several states to get 50+% of the votes.
Boy was I wrong (Jan 6) Boy was I wrong. I sent you an xls file named “worst jan 6 case”. I assumed civility&amp;hellip;
I did not guess we would have the “Trump Riots”</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
