<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My Dad&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My Dad&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mydadsblog.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>illusions</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/illusions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/illusions/</guid>
      <description>Remember M.C.Escher?
Back in the 70’s I worked on an advanced project to design a new computer language, and then write a compiler to translate that new language into machine code but using that new language itself to do the work. A compiler is a program which converts English language looking instructions into machine code which is a series of ones and zeros that the machine actually executes. We used that famous drawing of M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rant on Vaccine Efficacy</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/rant-on-vaccine-efficacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/rant-on-vaccine-efficacy/</guid>
      <description>A friend’s adult son was hesitant get a particular vaccine thinking one was a lot better than another. He had heard about the different “efficacy” rates. I also heard about a phlebotomist (the person who takes you blood) saying he was going to wait for “the vaccine for black people”. The latter worried me the most because that person is in the health care industry and is still poorly informed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rant on St Patrick</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/rant-on-st-patrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/rant-on-st-patrick/</guid>
      <description>St. Patrick, considered the patron saint of Ireland, was born in, a town in Roman Britain, sometime around 380 AD. He wrote in one of his writings:
 My name is Patrick. I am a sinner, a simple country person, and the least of all believers&amp;hellip; My father was Calpornius. He was a deacon; his father was Potitus, a priest, who lived at Bannavem Taburniae. His home was near there, and that is where I was taken prisoner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rant on Crispr</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/rant-on-crispr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/rant-on-crispr/</guid>
      <description>You have heard about CRISPR, I suspect. It is a gene-editing technology which can modify, delete or correct (modify) precise regions of DNA or RNA. If you want a treatise on the interaction of DNA and RNA, let me know. But in a drastic simplification: a DNA strand reproduces itself by breaking in specific places, uses RNA to make a copy of the DNA strands, and then reconnects the duplicated pieces to form a duplicate of the original.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Have a Friend</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/i-have-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/i-have-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>I have a friend (besides you) that produces TV shows. He told me something that depressed him, and myself. The TV network that his shows are produced under had to change the script of the shows to accommodate their audience. Their audience is skewed to one side of our political divide. He needed to change the flow of the script to not emphasize that COVID-19 was a real fact because that is what their audience believes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some of This Was Interesting</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/some-of-this-was-interesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/some-of-this-was-interesting/</guid>
      <description>They asked a population of people a series of questions, some true, some false, on subjects being discussed in the public at this time. All of the questions could absolutely be proven TRUE or FALSE (it was not a subjective topic). They then asked the person where they primarily got their information. The top of the graph I would have predicted. I did not expect the difference in the bottom two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Flu - A Rant</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/missing-flu-a-rant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/missing-flu-a-rant/</guid>
      <description>I started to follow the new mRNA technique of fighting “the flu” in 2018. It was novel because it was not trying to anticipate the internal DNA or internal RNA, but the external part of the virus. Rather than a specific antigen to what they guessed would be next year’s virus, it was thought that to attack the external attachment would be more general. Thus it was hoped to be a multiyear approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insurrection</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/insurrection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/insurrection/</guid>
      <description>14th amendment in part:
 No person shall be a Senator or Representative in Congress, or elector of President and Vice President, or hold any office, civil or military, under the United States, or under any State, who, having previously taken an oath, as a member of Congress, or as an officer of the United States, or as a member of any State legislature, or as an executive or judicial officer of any State, to support the Constitution of the United States, shall have engaged in insurrection or rebellion against the same, or given aid or comfort to the enemies thereof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Even if / Boy Was I Wrong</title>
      <link>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/so-even-if-boy-was-i-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mydadsblog.com/posts/so-even-if-boy-was-i-wrong/</guid>
      <description>(This was two emails, before and after the insurrection.)
So Even if (Jan 5) If any state’s electoral vote were excluded, the law also says it is excluded from the total. Thus Trump would need to exclude several states to get 50+% of the votes.
Boy was I wrong (Jan 6) Boy was I wrong. I sent you an xls file named “worst jan 6 case”. I assumed civility&amp;hellip;
I did not guess we would have the “Trump Riots”</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
